S-WEBSRV03 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-BBDS01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-DB01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDFS01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-UPS01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-DEPLOY01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDSH02 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-WEBSRV01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-VCSA01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-PRN01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-FS01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-DC01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDGW01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-MX02 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-LOG01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-XIBO01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDSH03 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
C-W7-IMMO ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-AV01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDAPP01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-MXARCH01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-WAHL01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-BACKUP01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-IGEL01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDSH04 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDSH01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-MON01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-WEBSRV02 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
C-WXP-WEIDA ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
C-W7-EDWALT3 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-CA01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-DC02 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
C-W7-PERSONAL ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-SCANNER01 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown
S-RDAPP02 ######  VMware tools detected. I will attempt to gracefully shutdown

#### Number of VMs that were Powered off ####
   Total of 0 VMs with no VMware Tools
   Total of 35 VMs with VMware Tools
   Total of 35 VMs Powered off
